好的，大家好，我叫Cody Baker，是大学三年级的学生
okay hello everyone my name is Cody Baker and a third year student in the
Baker and a third year student in the Department of a fighting computational
我系一所战斗计算数学与统计系学习
Department of a fighting computational mathematics and statistics and I study
mathematics and statistics and I study in computational neuroscience and
在计算神经科学中，特别是在推理问题上
in computational neuroscience and particular the problem of inferring
particular the problem of inferring neuronal network structure specifically
神经元网络结构，特别是来自细胞外的数据
neuronal network structure specifically with data coming from extracellular
with data coming from extracellular recording techniques so before we start
记录技术，所以在我们开始谈论结果之前，我们还要做一个
recording techniques so before we start to talk about results we also do a
to talk about results we also do a little bit of background in neuroscience
神经科学和我们现在使用的模型的背景知识很少
little bit of background in neuroscience and the models that we use now you don't
and the models that we use now you don't have to know too much but you do have to
必须了解太多，但是您必须知道大脑是一个器官
have to know too much but you do have to know that the brain is an organ
know that the brain is an organ comprised of very large numbers of
由非常多的单个计算单元组成，这些单元称为
comprised of very large numbers of individual computing unit cells known as
individual computing unit cells known as neurons and neurons are able to connect
神经元和神经元能够通过突触相互连接
neurons and neurons are able to connect to one another by way of a synapse which
to one another by way of a synapse which is when the axon extension of one neuron
当一个神经元的轴突延伸附着到另一个神经元的树突上时，
is when the axon extension of one neuron attaches to the dendrites of another and
attaches to the dendrites of another and they share information across the
它们通过电化学方式在整个突触中共享信息
they share information across the synapse by way of electrochemical
synapse by way of electrochemical impulses known as spikes these are brief
这些脉冲称为尖峰脉冲，是通过电压迹线可观察到的短暂瞬变
impulses known as spikes these are brief transients observable via voltage traces
transients observable via voltage traces from the inside of a neuron you see the
在神经元内部，您会看到尖峰是那里的两个大事件，
from the inside of a neuron you see the spikes are the two big events there and
spikes are the two big events there and they decay very quickly Dunn's back to
它们很快衰减邓恩回到了静止的电位
they decay very quickly Dunn's back to the resting potential
the resting potential now neurons come in two types excitatory
现在神经元有兴奋性和抑制性两种重要的区别
now neurons come in two types excitatory and inhibitory the important difference
and inhibitory the important difference is that the effect of spiking and a
是尖峰和突触前细胞的作用可能导致更多
is that the effect of spiking and a presynaptic cell can either cause more
presynaptic cell can either cause more or less light in the postsynaptic cell
或更少的突触后细胞和像你这样的聪明人的行为
or less light in the postsynaptic cell and intelligent behavior people like you
and intelligent behavior people like you and me are thought to arise by complex
我和我被认为是由于尖峰的复杂，非常复杂的相互作用而产生的
and me are thought to arise by complex very complex interactions of spiking
very complex interactions of spiking events in very large networks now there
大型网络中的事件现在有很多不同的计算
events in very large networks now there are a lot of different computational
are a lot of different computational theories that can explain very specific
可以解释非常具体的任务（例如记忆视觉）的理论
theories that can explain very specific tasks such as memory visual
tasks such as memory visual classification District in making go on
分类区仍在继续，但我们没有足够的实际数据来
classification District in making go on but we don't have enough real data to
but we don't have enough real data to confirm that of actual brains follow any
确认实际的大脑遵循任何特定的理论，其中很大一部分
confirm that of actual brains follow any specific theory and a big part of this
specific theory and a big part of this is because in the past people had been
是因为过去人们能够从我手中进行举报
is because in the past people had been able to report from my hands
able to report from my hands neurons simultaneously at a time there
最近一次同时出现神经元，并且这种情况一直在发展
neurons simultaneously at a time there recently and this has been developing
recently and this has been developing almost analogous to Moore's law every
每隔几年几乎类似于摩尔定律，我们找到一种方法来记录
almost analogous to Moore's law every few years we find a way to record from
few years we find a way to record from twice as many neurons as before in
近年来，我们开发的神经元数量是以前的两倍
twice as many neurons as before in recent years we have developed
recent years we have developed techniques that can record from hundreds
可以记录成千上万的技术我想现在他们正在开始
techniques that can record from hundreds thousands I think now they're starting
thousands I think now they're starting to push tens of thousands and we're
推动成千上万，我们将专注于一个
to push tens of thousands and we're going to focus on one in particular on
going to focus on one in particular on that that called calcium imaging now
所谓的钙成像现在可以主动成像了，您拥有中央激光
that that called calcium imaging now active imaging you have a central laser
active imaging you have a central laser hub is gaining gaining some cubic volume
集线器正在获得一些立方体积的神经空间和一大堆
hub is gaining gaining some cubic volume of neural space and a whole bunch of
of neural space and a whole bunch of post processing machine learning based
基于机器学习的后处理技术，您可以识别位置
post processing machine learning based techniques you can identify the location
techniques you can identify the location in space of every individual neuron and
在每个神经元的空间中，然后您就可以提取出
in space of every individual neuron and then you can extract a measure of
then you can extract a measure of fluorescence that indicates how active
荧光指示神经元的活跃度和个体性，这是
fluorescence that indicates how active and individual neuron is and this is
and individual neuron is and this is actual real data you're looking at here
您在这里查看的是实际的真实数据，您可以看到一些神经元在刺刺
actual real data you're looking at here and you can see some neurons are spiking
and you can see some neurons are spiking very frequently that's like that one
很多时候，就像那个总是彩色的Thurmont穗状花序
very frequently that's like that one that's always colored Thurmont spiking
that's always colored Thurmont spiking at all and others are going very
根本没有其他人根据最重要的内容进行
at all and others are going very sporadically according to what's on top
sporadically according to what's on top of these and so in the context of the
这些，因此在数据的上下文中，它看起来像什么
of these and so in the context of the data what does it look like it looks
data what does it look like it looks like a bunch of calcium sorry it looks
像一堆钙，对不起，它看起来像一堆高斯预言
like a bunch of calcium sorry it looks like a bunch of Gaussian Prophecy you
like a bunch of Gaussian Prophecy you get traces of relative fluorescence for
获得脸部每个像素的相对荧光的痕迹，这些是
get traces of relative fluorescence for every pixel in the face these are the
every pixel in the face these are the cameras
相机恒光束分束器
cameras constant optical beam splitter you
应该会自动学习下一个视频以跟随该视频，因此我是我的目标
should automatically learn to the next thing to follow that video so I my goal
thing to follow that video so I my goal here is to look at these traces as
这里是将这些痕迹视为高斯过程，并试图猜测
here is to look at these traces as Gaussian processes and to try to guess
Gaussian processes and to try to guess which neurons are connected to one
哪些神经元相互连接，我们可以从统计学上对马尔维斯
which neurons are connected to one another and we can statistically maulvis
another and we can statistically maulvis data in a number of different ways we
我们可以使用多种不同的方式使用随机微分方程
data in a number of different ways we can use stochastic differential equation
can use stochastic differential equation for linear dynamical systems we talked
对于线性动力系统，我们在课堂上讨论了通用自回归
for linear dynamical systems we talked about in class general auto regressive
about in class general auto regressive processes or any sort of time series
流程或任何时间序列模型，并且由于我们正在尝试
processes or any sort of time series model and since we're trying to go a
model and since we're trying to go a little faster today I probably won't
今天快一点，我可能不会在模型上谈论太多凝胶
little faster today I probably won't talk too much about the gel on models
talk too much about the gel on models okay so in the context of everything
好的，所以在今天我们要谈论的所有事情的背景下，
okay so in the context of everything we're going to talk about today we're
we're going to talk about today we're always going to be referencing an
总是要引用一个邻接矩阵或我们的概率
always going to be referencing an adjacency matrix or our probabilistic
adjacency matrix or our probabilistic graphical models shown by this network
该网络显示的图形模型现在可分解为两个不同的
graphical models shown by this network now it is decomposable into two distinct
now it is decomposable into two distinct parts it has a weighted part that is
它有一个加权的部分，它是随机的并且是正态分布的，并且
parts it has a weighted part that is random and normally distributed and it
random and normally distributed and it has a structure driven by what's called
具有所谓的进一步旅程驱动的结构，这意味着
has a structure driven by what's called further journey which has means it's
further journey which has means it's random binary at some level it's party
在某种程度上它是聚会的随机二进制，所以这是一个示例邻接矩阵
random binary at some level it's party so this is an example adjacency matrix
so this is an example adjacency matrix remember it's back wise because we have
记住这是明智的，因为我们的大脑中有兴奋性和抑制性神经元
remember it's back wise because we have excitatory and inhibitory neurons in our
excitatory and inhibitory neurons in our model and here you continue inhibitory
模型，在这里您继续抑制性的总是有负权重，所以您
model and here you continue inhibitory ones always have negative weights so you
ones always have negative weights so you have random winding and spar structure
最重要的是具有随机的绕组和翼梁结构，并明确说明
have random winding and spar structure on top of that and explicitly stating
on top of that and explicitly stating the problem we're interested in
我们感兴趣的问题是，我们将稀疏结构Omega或
the problem we're interested in differing the sparse structure Omega or
differing the sparse structure Omega or the undirected case of Omega plus Omega
欧米茄加欧米茄转置的无方向案例
the undirected case of Omega plus Omega transpose
transpose and the quick note on this topic before
在我们进行稳定性之前就此主题进行快速注释是非常重要的
and the quick note on this topic before we go on stability is a very important
we go on stability is a very important issue with these networks and you need
这些网络的问题，您需要一组非常具体的约束来
issue with these networks and you need very specific set of constraints to
very specific set of constraints to guarantee that your system is always
确保您的系统始终稳定，并通过应用1
guarantee that your system is always stable and you do that by applying a 1
stable and you do that by applying a 1 over square root and scaling on the
超过平方根并按正态分布的捕捉缩放表示
over square root and scaling on the normally distributed snap express that
normally distributed snap express that constrains a vast majority of the
将绝大多数特征值限制在单位圆内，但是
constrains a vast majority of the eigenvalues to the unit circle and but
eigenvalues to the unit circle and but then you'll notice you have these two
然后您会注意到您拥有这两个共轭的大特征值
then you'll notice you have these two big eigen values that are conjugate
big eigen values that are conjugate pairs those are related to the Kurdish
对那些与库尔德人有关的结构的稀疏性和
pairs those are related to the Kurdish for any structure the sparsity and those
for any structure the sparsity and those you can keep to the right simply by
您可以通过这两个陪审团的条件简单地保持在右边
you can keep to the right simply by these two jury conditions the
these two jury conditions the determinant of the trace on the block
块上轨迹的决定因素在于网络的平均值，
determinant of the trace on the block lies average for the network and
lies average for the network and throughout this we're going to be
在这整个过程中，我们将量化各种性能
throughout this we're going to be quantifying the performance of various
quantifying the performance of various algorithms using policy analysis and
使用策略分析的算法以及是否比第一次看到它或
algorithms using policy analysis and whether than first time seeing it or
whether than first time seeing it or just need a little refresher the ROC
只需稍微刷新一下，ROC曲线就为false的参数函数
just need a little refresher the ROC curve is a parametric function of false
curve is a parametric function of false positive rate versus true positive rate
正比率与真正比率作为线性分类器的阈值
positive rate versus true positive rate as the threshold of a linear classifier
as the threshold of a linear classifier is buried and so this is an example
被埋了，所以这是我们要去做的一些东西的盗版曲线的例子
is buried and so this is an example Piracy curve for some stuff we're going
Piracy curve for some stuff we're going to talk about in just a bit
谈论一下，你会看到你得到很高的真实
to talk about in just a bit and you can see you get very high true
and you can see you get very high true positives for very low false positives
积极性极低的误报率，但总的来说，我们经常会感兴趣
positives for very low false positives but overall we will often be interested
but overall we will often be interested only in the area under this curve which
仅在此曲线下方的区域内，才是1/2之间的好才华
only in the area under this curve which is a nice talented measure between 1/2
is a nice talented measure between 1/2 and 1 corresponding to just random
和1对应于随机猜测和完美分类
and 1 corresponding to just random guessing and perfect classification
guessing and perfect classification respectively okay so the case model
分别好吧，所以我们将简要讨论的案例模型是
respectively okay so the case model we'll talk briefly about is the
we'll talk briefly about is the stochastic differential equation which
随机微分方程是一种威尔逊考文率模型，可以
stochastic differential equation which is a Wilson cowan rate model which can
is a Wilson cowan rate model which can be expressed as this equation in terms
用该方程的随机微分表示为
be expressed as this equation in terms of the stochastic differential of the
of the stochastic differential of the white noise which is just the
白噪声，这只是耳朵获利过程的差异，但
white noise which is just the differential of ear profit process but
differential of ear profit process but if you just back up and look at it it's
如果您只是备份并查看它，实际上只是一个箭头，
if you just back up and look at it it's really just an arrow one process in
really just an arrow one process in continuous time so we know how to deal
连续的时间，所以我们知道如何处理
continuous time so we know how to deal with this
with this and you know the most useful thing that
您知道我们将使用此方程式最有用的是
and you know the most useful thing that we will use this equation for is the
we will use this equation for is the fact that has analytical solutions to
对诸如交叉协方差之类的东西具有解析解的事实
fact that has analytical solutions to stuff like the cross cross covariance
stuff like the cross cross covariance and in particular the cross spectrum
特别是交叉谱，它是傅立叶变换的傅立叶变换
and in particular the cross spectrum which is the Fourier transform of that
which is the Fourier transform of that the specific algebraic form of the zero
零频率互谱的特定代数形式可以是
the specific algebraic form of the zero frequency cross spectrum can be
frequency cross spectrum can be explicitly expanded to give a one-to-one
明确扩展以提供双向之间的一对一关系
explicitly expanded to give a one-to-one relationship between bi-directional
relationship between bi-directional connectivity and precision so this is
连通性和精确度，所以这有点像所有
connectivity and precision so this is kind of like an analogous to all the
kind of like an analogous to all the stuff we talked about with Gaussian
我们讨论过的与高斯图形模型有关的东西，除了这是一个
stuff we talked about with Gaussian graphical models except this is a
graphical models except this is a process that's varying in time and so
过程是随时间变化的，因此您可以等效地表示为贷款
process that's varying in time and so you can equivalently express as a loan
you can equivalently express as a loan process and disclose form as an LDS that
处理和披露作为LDS的表格，在此过程中我们已经看到了很多
process and disclose form as an LDS that we've seen a lot of throughout this
we've seen a lot of throughout this class and there are a lot of different
班级，并且有很多与次理想相关的次要问题
class and there are a lot of different sub problems related to sub ideal
sub problems related to sub ideal observations you can have more
在模型中，您可以拥有比神经元更多的观察结果
observations you can have more observations than neurons in the model
observations than neurons in the model that's a great problem to have because
这是一个很大的问题，因为那时您有多个样本
that's a great problem to have because then you have multiple samples from
then you have multiple samples from every neuron but it's often not the case
每个神经元，但通常情况并非如此，通常是因为您的观察次数较少
every neuron but it's often not the case often times you have fewer observations
often times you have fewer observations than you do neurons in which case you
而不是神经元，在这种情况下，您几乎必须转移整个神经元
than you do neurons in which case you pretty much have to shift the entire
pretty much have to shift the entire argument around not talking about
关于不讨论推断单个神经元连通性的争论，但
argument around not talking about inferring single neuron connectivity but
inferring single neuron connectivity but other connectivity between multiple
我知道多个神经元局部和空间之间的其他连通性
other connectivity between multiple neurons local and space I know the
neurons local and space I know the really hard problem is you can have
真正困难的问题是您可以有不同数量的观测值
really hard problem is you can have different numbers of observations
different numbers of observations throughout time whenever you apply
在任何时候，只要您应用钙成像，就将其应用到
throughout time whenever you apply calcium imaging you're applying it to a
calcium imaging you're applying it to a live subject and so they are sometimes
生活对象，因此有时会麻醉以尽量减少了解
live subject and so they are sometimes anesthetized to try to minimize knowing
anesthetized to try to minimize knowing but there's always a little bit of
但是总会有一点抖动和一点动静，所以
but there's always a little bit of jitter a little bit of movement and so
jitter a little bit of movement and so you always have to be able to try to
您必须始终能够尝试识别出您所处的神经元集合
you always have to be able to try to identify the set of neurons that you are
identify the set of neurons that you are somehow reporting from constantly
始终不断地进行报告，并一起编写所有内容
somehow reporting from constantly throughout time and write together all
throughout time and write together all the data samples from that but my focus
数据样本，但是我今天的重点是更基本的
the data samples from that but my focus today is on a more fundamental
today is on a more fundamental difficulty so justr simplicity let's
困难，所以简单一点，让我们假设我们有近乎完美的观察结果
difficulty so justr simplicity let's assume we have near-perfect observations
assume we have near-perfect observations for the LDL
对于LDL，所以当我们有一个线性
for the LDL so we're gonna do when we have a linear
so we're gonna do when we have a linear dynamical system well the best way to
动态系统最好的推断参数的方法是
dynamical system well the best way to get inference of parameters is
get inference of parameters is expectation-maximization right you've
期望最大化，您已经运行了卡尔曼滤波和平滑处理
expectation-maximization right you've run the Kalman filtering and smoothing
run the Kalman filtering and smoothing by Muslims passing and then you get a
由穆斯林经过，然后您会在某些初始值上获得速率DM算法
by Muslims passing and then you get a rate DM algorithm on some initial
rate DM algorithm on some initial guesses and after the few iterations
猜测，经过几次迭代，它将收敛，这是一个示例
guesses and after the few iterations it'll converge and this is an example
it'll converge and this is an example application of it you see a true network
应用它，您会在左侧看到一个真正的网络，然后您就拥有了
application of it you see a true network there up on the left and then you have
there up on the left and then you have an estimate given out a fixed false
给出固定的误报率的估算值，因此该估算值
an estimate given out a fixed false positive ratio so this estimate of the
positive ratio so this estimate of the network was chosen to be right about
在ROC曲线上选择的网络就在那附近，
network was chosen to be right about there on the ROC curve to live there to
there on the ROC curve to live there to have a similar level of sparsity and a
具有相似的稀疏度和相当高的信心
have a similar level of sparsity and a fairly high degree of confidence that
fairly high degree of confidence that the selected edges are in fact true
选定的边缘实际上是真实的边缘，但最重要的是
the selected edges are in fact true edges but the most important thing here
edges but the most important thing here is the fact that the area under the ROC
是ROC曲线下的面积单调增加的事实
is the fact that the area under the ROC curve monotonically increases that you
curve monotonically increases that you feed it more and more data in near will
几乎以数十到数百的规模向其提供越来越多的数据
feed it more and more data in near will on the scale of tens to hundreds of
on the scale of tens to hundreds of thousands of data samples that will
数以千计的数据样本将很快变得非常重要，
thousands of data samples that will become very important just a second and
become very important just a second and you can also see that it converging to a
您还可以看到，对于这些简单的方法，它已经收敛到一个完美的分类器
you can also see that it converging to a perfect classifier for it these simple
perfect classifier for it these simple networks now why is it we know that if
网络现在为什么会这样？我们知道，如果您只有ggm，那就有一个标准
networks now why is it we know that if you just have a ggm there's a standard
you just have a ggm there's a standard time invariant graph we can explicitly
时不变图，我们可以显式地得到一组条件
time invariant graph we can explicitly get to a set of conditional
get to a set of conditional independencies from the precision maker
来自精密制造商的独立性，我们知道，但是精密矩阵是
independencies from the precision maker we know that but the precision matrix is
we know that but the precision matrix is just one type of a general idea that's
只是一般概念的一种，称为偏相关和粒子
just one type of a general idea that's called partial correlation and particle
called partial correlation and particle relations are really just pairwise
关系实际上只是基于一组的成对相关
relations are really just pairwise correlations conditioned on from set of
correlations conditioned on from set of the network and precision is in fact the
网络和精度实际上是
the network and precision is in fact the largest type of partial correlation in
largest type of partial correlation in the sense of you condition on everything
除了平价以外，您的感觉还取决于网络上的其他所有内容
the sense of you condition on everything else on the network besides the parity
else on the network besides the parity that you're looking at but expectation
您正在查看的商品，但期望最大化也可以看作是
that you're looking at but expectation maximization can also be viewed as a
maximization can also be viewed as a type of partial correlation if you look
如果查看我们在作业5中得出的值，则是部分相关的类型
type of partial correlation if you look at the values we derived in homework 5
at the values we derived in homework 5 or in the equivalent common estimate
或在等价的共同估算中，您可以看到您的数量是
or in the equivalent common estimate you can see you have quantities that are
you can see you have quantities that are essentially proportional to the 0 large
基本上与每个学生的0个大样本成正比
essentially proportional to the 0 large sample per student being projected in
sample per student being projected in the direction of the live 1 cross
实时1交叉协方差的方向，因为记住eeehm给
the direction of the live 1 cross covariance because remember eeehm gives
covariance because remember eeehm gives us a directed measure whereas precision
我们采用有针对性的措施，而精度是您必须施加的对称值
us a directed measure whereas precision is a symmetric value you have to impose
is a symmetric value you have to impose some sort of directionality in some way
某种程度上的方向性，还有很多其他不同
some sort of directionality in some way and there are a lot of other different
and there are a lot of other different methods but I thought that was kind of
方法，但我认为pm确实只是一个
methods but I thought that was kind of interesting that p.m. is really just a
interesting that p.m. is really just a special case of correlation okay we
相关的特殊情况好吗，我们讨论过直接估算
special case of correlation okay we talked about directly estimating the
talked about directly estimating the precision instead of doing the common
精度，而不是做普通的事情，经验数据的一个大问题是
precision instead of doing the common stuff a big issue with empirical data is
stuff a big issue with empirical data is you have very short duration of trials
您的试用期非常短，通常在几秒钟到
you have very short duration of trials typically in the order of seconds to
typically in the order of seconds to minutes if that aware is the plot that I
分钟，如果那是我刚刚向您展示的情节
minutes if that aware is the plot that I was just showing you where
was just showing you where expectation-maximization converged to a
在ROC曲线下，期望最大化收敛到一个非常好的区域
expectation-maximization converged to a really good area under the ROC curve you
really good area under the ROC curve you needed hundreds of thousands of data
需要成千上万的数据样本，这等于让您
needed hundreds of thousands of data samples that would equate to having you
samples that would equate to having you know trials that lasted for several
知道审判已经持续了几个小时现在不切实际没有生命
know trials that lasted for several hours now not just impractical no living
hours now not just impractical no living subject wants to sit there and watching
对象想要坐在那里看电影，通常要花三个小时
subject wants to sit there and watching movies with three hours these typically
movies with three hours these typically might have to deal with so we have very
可能需要处理，所以我们只有很少的数据，因此可以更好地利用
might have to deal with so we have very little data and so to make better use of
little data and so to make better use of what little data we have we will use the
我们拥有多少数据，我们将使用正则化这个流行词，因此
what little data we have we will use the buzzword of regularization and so the
buzzword of regularization and so the beijing of perspective regularization is
透视正则化的北京实际上就像应用先验
beijing of perspective regularization is really just like applying a prior
really just like applying a prior distribution to the coefficients for
某些回归模型的系数分布以及与
distribution to the coefficients for some regression model and concerning the
some regression model and concerning the model in that way really makes better
这样的模型实际上可以更好地利用您所提供的数据
model in that way really makes better use of what data you have they it gives
use of what data you have they it gives you a higher-quality estimate for
您将获得较高质量的估算值，以获取舒适的数据量，因此
you a higher-quality estimate for comfortable amounts of data and so the
comfortable amounts of data and so the specific estimation approach for
我将使用的具体估计方法是图形化的
specific estimation approach for proceeding that I will use is graphical
proceeding that I will use is graphical lasso a very popular approach very
套索一种非常流行的方法，非常流行的算法，如果解决方案
lasso a very popular approach very popular algorithm and if the solution of
popular algorithm and if the solution of this optimization equation where you'll
这个优化方程式，您会在这里注意到，我们对它使用l1范数
this optimization equation where you'll notice here we're using an l1 norm on
notice here we're using an l1 norm on our regularization that is
我们的正规化就像在我们的身上加了一个稀疏的传单
our regularization that is like imposing a sparse flyer on our
like imposing a sparse flyer on our precision matrix and the regularization
精度矩阵和可选择数量的正则强度Ram
precision matrix and the regularization strength Ram that can be chosen a number
strength Ram that can be chosen a number of different ways the simplest way is to
最简单的方法是针对目标bono进行交叉验证
of different ways the simplest way is to cross validated against target bono
cross validated against target bono sparsity the far more interesting
稀疏性更有趣的方法是使用一种称为
sparsity the far more interesting approach is to use something called the
approach is to use something called the Stars algorithm which uses all sorts of
采用各种措施（例如基于体育的基特维奇运动）的明星算法
Stars algorithm which uses all sorts of measures like kitv icy sports-based
measures like kitv icy sports-based criterion and it runs all these to
准则，并且将所有这些运行到各种迭代中，以产生一种
criterion and it runs all these to various iterations to kind of produce a
various iterations to kind of produce a target level of expected sparsity and so
目标稀疏度的水平，因此如果您使用饼图Galasso
target level of expected sparsity and so if you a pie graph Galasso and in
if you a pie graph Galasso and in combination with a number of other
结合许多其他措施，您会发现到目前为止
combination with a number of other measures you'll notice that by far it
measures you'll notice that by far it always surpasses every other measure for
在这些类型的
always surpasses every other measure for in terms of structure in these types of
in terms of structure in these types of networks and here are notice the
网络，这是以前注意到的T规模的差异
networks and here are notice the difference in the scale of T previously
difference in the scale of T previously we were talking about tens hundreds of
我们现在谈论的是成千上万的数据点
we were talking about tens hundreds of thousands of data points now we're
thousands of data points now we're talking about hundreds which is why our
谈论数百个，这就是为什么我们知道恢复不是那么好
talking about hundreds which is why our you know it recovery isn't that great
you know it recovery isn't that great but the point is still that crossover
但重点仍然是，交叉功能比其他任何功能都好得多
but the point is still that crossover does a far better job than any other
does a far better job than any other algorithm including the naive estimate
包括天真的精度估计（仅是反函数）的算法
algorithm including the naive estimate of precision which is just the inverse
of precision which is just the inverse of sample covariance okay but there's a
样本协方差还可以，但是我们有一个很大的不现实的假设
of sample covariance okay but there's a big unrealistic assumption that we've
big unrealistic assumption that we've made throughout all the models so far
到目前为止，在所有模型中都进行了建模，现在缺少外部输入
made throughout all the models so far and that's a lack of external input now
and that's a lack of external input now in in empirical studies you never have
在实证研究中，您永远不会观察到这些东西，因此它们
in in empirical studies you never have observations of these things and so they
observations of these things and so they take on the role of latent variables
承担潜在变量的角色，这使它们很难处理
take on the role of latent variables which makes them very difficult to deal
which makes them very difficult to deal with and the way to interpret the
解释外部输入的方法通常在皮质中
with and the way to interpret the external inputs is typically in cortex
external inputs is typically in cortex you have multiple recurrent layers where
您有多个循环层，其中一个主题的前馈可提供
you have multiple recurrent layers where one subject's feed-forward offers
one subject's feed-forward offers heapsort projections onto the other
堆排序投射到另一个上，通常只是兴奋性的
heapsort projections onto the other and typically it's only excitatory
and typically it's only excitatory neurons that do that as well so they
神经元也这样做，因此它们承担了潜在变量的作用，
neurons that do that as well so they take on the role of latent variables and
take on the role of latent variables and so you can update the FTEs and
因此，您可以按照以下方式更新FTE和过渡模型：添加一个
so you can update the FTEs and transition models as follows you add a
transition models as follows you add a mean drive from some external adjacent
是指我们从某些外部邻近地点驱车而来，因此教堂非常相似
mean drive from some external adjacent we made church so it's very similar in
we made church so it's very similar in structure to the recurrent but typically
经常性的结构，但通常是矩形，您通常可以
structure to the recurrent but typically rectangular could you typically have
rectangular could you typically have more or less number of neurons and then
或多或少的神经元数量，然后您现在还具有相关的噪声项
more or less number of neurons and then you also now have correlated noise terms
you also now have correlated noise terms where B is the trusty decomposition of
其中B是外部协方差矩阵gamma的可信赖分解
where B is the trusty decomposition of the external covariance matrix gamma and
the external covariance matrix gamma and so there's been some proposals on the
所以关于文学的一些建议至少可以在
so there's been some proposals on the literature that you can at least in the
literature that you can at least in the case of low rank external input where
低级外部输入的情况下，您只有少量神经元
case of low rank external input where you just have a handful of neurons in
you just have a handful of neurons in the external population there there's
有人建议您可以使用高斯
the external population there there's been proposed that you can use Gaussian
been proposed that you can use Gaussian process factor analysis to fit those
过程因子分析以适合那些照明尺寸，并且应该
process factor analysis to fit those lighting dimensions and that should
lighting dimensions and that should improve your estimate unfortunately I
不幸的是我提高了您的估计
improve your estimate unfortunately I tried and tried and tried to get this to
tried and tried and tried to get this to work unfortunately it appears is it
不幸的是，如果使用GP FA的话，它是否适合该过程？
work unfortunately it appears is it using GP FA over fits the process if
using GP FA over fits the process if it's not only the latent variables but
不仅是潜在变量，还有一些有价值的信息
it's not only the latent variables but some of the valuable information from
some of the valuable information from the stochastic process itself and so he
随机过程本身，所以他写了C Grasso用于残差
the stochastic process itself and so he written C Grasso used on the residuals
written C Grasso used on the residuals before and after an application of GP FA
在应用GP FA之前和之后以及GP FA的过度装配导致
before and after an application of GP FA and the overfitting from GP FA causes it
and the overfitting from GP FA causes it to decay a little lower it's also very
衰减得更低一点对于大型网络来说，算法也非常慢
to decay a little lower it's also very very slow algorithms for larger networks
very slow algorithms for larger networks so it's not considered practical
因此目前尚不实用
so it's not considered practical currently
currently okay and a quick note the problem at
好的，快速注意一下，至少持续平均上升的问题可以
okay and a quick note the problem at least of having a mean constant rise can
least of having a mean constant rise can be solved in the context of a linear
在线性动力系统中解决，这是一个荷马问题
be solved in the context of a linear dynamical system this is a Homer problem
dynamical system this is a Homer problem and vicious machine learning books
和恶意机器学习书籍第13部分，基本上，您只需添加一些
and vicious machine learning books section 13 basically you just add some
section 13 basically you just add some additional rows to your hidden States
隐藏状态的其他行现在可以统一解决，可以吸收
additional rows to your hidden States fix them at unity now you can absorb
fix them at unity now you can absorb additional columns as the main input
额外的列作为新网络W的主要输入，
additional columns as the main input onto your new network W and that
onto your new network W and that districts the whole problem but your ovm
确定整个问题所在，但您的ovm估计仍然可以
districts the whole problem but your ovm estimates would still be perfectly fine
estimates would still be perfectly fine unfortunately it doesn't appear to work
不幸的是，它似乎也不起作用，我们将解释为什么
unfortunately it doesn't appear to work either and we'll explain why in just a
either and we'll explain why in just a second okay we're back to the level
其次，我们回到了拥有成千上万数据的水平
second okay we're back to the level where we have tens of thousands of data
where we have tens of thousands of data samples so they should be doing better
样本，所以他们应该做得更好，但是不是
samples so they should be doing better right but they're not this is in the
right but they're not this is in the presence of external input Hackney has a
外部输入的存在哈克尼有一个潜在变量，所以为什么不
presence of external input Hackney has a latent variables and so why is not a
latent variables and so why is not a single measure giving us good influence
单项措施能给我们带来良好的影响，这是因为我们现在受到偏见
single measure giving us good influence it's because we are now receiving biased
it's because we are now receiving biased external input covariance that in fact
实际上与主输入驱动器共享项的外部输入协方差
external input covariance that in fact shares terms with the main input drive
shares terms with the main input drive so at least expectation-maximization you
所以至少要期望最大化，您现在必须完全重做最后一步
so at least expectation-maximization you have to completely redo the end step now
have to completely redo the end step now I've tried to do this analytically
不幸的是，我尝试过分析这一点，其中有一个特定的部分
I've tried to do this analytically unfortunately there is one specific part
unfortunately there is one specific part that is essentially intractable and so
这本质上是棘手的，所以您需要实施概括
that is essentially intractable and so you would need to implement generalize
you would need to implement generalize DM to a box made a local pollution but
DM到盒子里造成了局部污染，但现在通常没有其他措施
DM to a box made a local pollution but now generally none of the other measures
now generally none of the other measures work well either sample precision
样本精度协方差都很好，即使它们都不适合
work well either sample precision covariance even they are fit none of
covariance even they are fit none of them did a good job because they're all
他们做得很好，因为它们在某种程度上都具有精度的功能
them did a good job because they're all somehow functions of the precision for
somehow functions of the precision for this process which in the presence of an
在有外部输入的情况下进行以下过程的过程
this process which in the presence of an external input takes on the following
external input takes on the following form where you have additive terms going
从外部输入协方差得到附加项的表格
form where you have additive terms going from the external input covariance and
from the external input covariance and remember this is the part that gives us
记住这是给我们两个一对一关系的部分
remember this is the part that gives us two one-to-one relationship with
two one-to-one relationship with bi-directional network connectivity it's
双向网络连接，现在所有设备都在争先恐后地进行投影。
bi-directional network connectivity it's now being scrambled projected in all
now being scrambled projected in all sorts of different directions by the XR
XR 1的各种不同方向的协方差，您也得到了
sorts of different directions by the XR 1 for covariance and you're also getting
1 for covariance and you're also getting more very
从三重乘积项来看，更多的是
more very from the triple product term so it's
from the triple product term so it's just not a good problem and then yeah I
只是不是一个好问题，然后是的，我才刚刚开始获得系统
just not a good problem and then yeah I just we just started to get systems
just we just started to get systems we're going a little faster today quick
今天我们要快一点，快速将我的合作伙伴插入其中
we're going a little faster today quick plug my collaborators on a lot of this
plug my collaborators on a lot of this research at Rice University in Houston
休斯敦莱斯大学的研究由Ginevra Allen实验室负责
research at Rice University in Houston is headed by the lab of Ginevra Allen
is headed by the lab of Ginevra Allen they were exploring a couple other cases
他们正在探索其他一些时间依赖性的案例，这些案例确实
they were exploring a couple other cases of time dependence which are really
of time dependence which are really interesting that I don't have to talk
有趣的是，我不必在接下来的演讲中谈论
interesting that I don't have to talk about just as an upcoming talk next
about just as an upcoming talk next Friday May 4th that's a part of a team
5月4日，星期五，这是团队讨论会的一部分，但我认为这是
Friday May 4th that's a part of a team that's colloquium but I think it's
that's colloquium but I think it's sponsored by IBM he really goes there
在IBM的赞助下，他真的很感兴趣与高水平的人打交道。
sponsored by IBM he really goes there interested in dealing with high
interested in dealing with high dimensional data as she does a lot of
维度数据，因为她做了很多其他项目和生物统计学而不是
dimensional data as she does a lot of other projects and biostatistics not
other projects and biostatistics not just neuroscience and so here are many
只是神经科学，所以这里有许多其他参考资料允许
just neuroscience and so here are many other references that allow this is
other references that allow this is based on the first two were kind of
基于前两个是艾伦（Allen）的联合出版物，这是
based on the first two were kind of joint publications by Allen and this is
joint publications by Allen and this is just a general background on the problem
只是关于这个问题的一般背景，而只是要谈论
just a general background on the problem in general and simply gonna talk about
in general and simply gonna talk about GL and say if you want to learn more
GL，如果您想了解更多有关什么基因组可以提供任何信息的信息，
GL and say if you want to learn more about what genomes can offer any
about what genomes can offer any publication hospital lab is the way to
出版物医院实验室是工作的一种方式，它的工作受到多个方面的支持
publication hospital lab is the way to go it's work is supported under multiple
go it's work is supported under multiple NSF grants not like to thank everyone in
NSF赠款不希望感谢Rosenbaum实验室中的每个人对
NSF grants not like to thank everyone in the Rosenbaum lab for their feedback on
the Rosenbaum lab for their feedback on the early versions of this presentation
此演示文稿的早期版本，非常感谢您的收听，您呢？
the early versions of this presentation so thank you for listening and do you
so thank you for listening and do you have any questions
有任何疑问
是的
so thank you for listening and do you have any questions
yes
好吧，所以他都问我要看多少个神经元，所以我看了beta
okay so everything he asked how many neurons do I look at so I looked at beta
neurons do I look at so I looked at beta test containing hundreds but everything
测试包含数百个，但您在此演示文稿中看到的所有内容均为30
test containing hundreds but everything you saw in this presentation had was 30
you saw in this presentation had was 30 so very small Network now I have with
现在我的网络非常小，有成千上万个神经元插头
so very small Network now I have with that hundreds and thousands plug neuron
that hundreds and thousands plug neuron of neurons in the context of in silico
计算机模拟中神经元的数量，而您唯一的是
of neurons in the context of in silico modeling and you the only thing is it's
modeling and you the only thing is it's harder to get really clear results to
很难获得真正清晰的结果，以表明您可以提高
harder to get really clear results to show you you can crank up the data that
show you you can crank up the data that you feed the model do really like
您提供的模型确实确实像数百万个数据点，那就是
you feed the model do really like millions of data points and that's
millions of data points and that's what's required to get really good
要获得一生中真正好的推论，您需要什么？
what's required to get really good inference for life you know a thousand
inference for life you know a thousand neurons or something like that so yeah I
神经元之类的东西，所以是的，我看着这个很小的网络
neurons or something like that so yeah I looked at fairly small networks in this
looked at fairly small networks in this context but the goal is to develop
上下文，但目标是开发方法，但有其原因
context but the goal is to develop methods but there the reason there is
methods but there the reason there is computational time glosso doesn't even
如果您有几个以上的时间，那么计算时间的词汇表甚至无法收敛
computational time glosso doesn't even converge if you have more than a few
converge if you have more than a few hundred neurons there's a certain step
一百个神经元套索算法中有一个特定步骤
hundred neurons there's a certain step in the lasso algorithm where you have to
in the lasso algorithm where you have to do a kind of shooting thing and it just
做一种射击的事情，如果你不收敛就需要永远
do a kind of shooting thing and it just it takes forever to not converge if you
it takes forever to not converge if you have a few hundred neurons and very
有几百个神经元和非常少量的数据
have a few hundred neurons and very small amounts of data
但希望是有一天，我们会花所有的方法来解决这种情况
but the hope is to one day spend all of our methods to the case where we can
our methods to the case where we can look at tens of thousands simultaneously
同时看成千上万，仍然执行此级别的
look at tens of thousands simultaneously and still perform this level of
and still perform this level of inference we're just not there yet good
推断我们还不存在好问题，其他的都对，谢谢
inference we're just not there yet good question and the others right thank you
大家下午好，我的演讲是关于基于Web的树状结构
so good afternoon everybody my talk is about web-based tree-structured
about web-based tree-structured compressive sensing with variation of
贝叶斯分析和小波变换的压缩感知
compressive sensing with variation of Bayesian analysis so and wavelet based
Bayesian analysis so and wavelet based transform can be used to decompose a
变换可用于分解我们具有的给定信号或函数
transform can be used to decompose a given signal or function that we have in
given signal or function that we have in terms of some basic functions called
一些称为小波的基本函数的术语，然后我们可以研究这些
terms of some basic functions called wavelets and then we can study these the
wavelets and then we can study these the structure of these wavelet coefficients
这些小波系数的结构适合填充我们拥有的数据
structure of these wavelet coefficients proper to fill data that we have so
proper to fill data that we have so imagine that we have a signal and we
想象一下，我们有一个信号，然后应用是否在此构成
imagine that we have a signal and we apply whether the composition on this
apply whether the composition on this the results are two types of data one is
结果是两种类型的数据，一种是缩放系数，另一种是
the results are two types of data one is the scaling coefficients the other ones
the scaling coefficients the other ones are the favorite coefficient scaling
最喜欢的系数缩放系数给出的近似值是
are the favorite coefficient scaling coefficients give an approximation of
coefficients give an approximation of the function that we have in some lower
我们在较低分辨率的空间中具有的功能
the function that we have in some lower resolution space and the other
resolution space and the other coefficient provides us with the detail
系数为我们提供了重建原始图像所需的细节
coefficient provides us with the detail that we need to reconstruct the original
that we need to reconstruct the original data that we have from those that
从这些近似数据中得到的数据现在我们可以应用
data that we have from those that approximation now we can apply the
approximation now we can apply the wavelet decomposition as many at times
小波分解的次数是我们想要的，每次都需要
wavelet decomposition as many at times as we want and each time we need to take
as we want and each time we need to take the product mission that we have why the
我们有产品任务，为什么要对此进行合成，然后我们最终
the product mission that we have why the composition on that and then we end up
composition on that and then we end up with another set of reverberate
另一组回响系数甚至更低的分辨率
with another set of reverberate coefficient and even lower resolution of
coefficient and even lower resolution of the approximation so to reconstruct the
近似，以便重建数据，并且
the approximation so to reconstruct the data which and
我们可以采用这些开尔文系数并将其与天气情况相加
we can take these Kelvin coefficients and sum them with the weather conditions
and sum them with the weather conditions that we have for all the levels of
我们具有所有分解水平，并且我们重建了
that we have for all the levels of decomposition and we reconstruct our
decomposition and we reconstruct our original data so for most ignores the
原始数据，因此对于大多数人而言，小波系数是不可或缺的
original data so for most ignores the wavelet coefficients are part and
wavelet coefficients are part and they're compressible and that means that
它们是可压缩的，这意味着我们可以将许多豁免设置为零
they're compressible and that means that we can set to zero many of the waiver
we can set to zero many of the waiver coefficients that we have many of them
我们拥有许多系数，它们的价值微不足道，我们可以忽略不计
coefficients that we have many of them have negligible value and we can neglect
have negligible value and we can neglect them and we can reconstruct the function
他们，我们可以从修改后的小波系数重建函数
them and we can reconstruct the function from the modified wavelet coefficients
from the modified wavelet coefficients and end up with a good very accurately
并最终获得非常准确的结果，因为我们拥有的测量
and end up with a good very accurately because the measurements that we have
because the measurements that we have might not might not always be easy and
可能并不总是容易且便宜地获取，例如在MRI中
might not might not always be easy and cheap to acquire for example in MRI
cheap to acquire for example in MRI image imaging it's very tedious faster
图像成像非常繁琐，需要耗时的成像
image imaging it's very tedious faster it's time-consuming imaging we need to
it's time-consuming imaging we need to take image in many spiritual bands so
在许多精神团体中拍摄图像，所以人们可能会认为这是有用的方法
take image in many spiritual bands so one might think that it's the useful way
one might think that it's the useful way to only measure the informative data
仅测量信息量
我们需要进行的测量，因此我们假设不可压缩的测试是
one might think that it's the useful way to only measure the informative data
measurements that we need to have so the incompressible testing we assume that
我们需要进行的测量，因此我们假设不可压缩的测试是
incompressible testing we assume that the signal we have is compressible
我们拥有的信号是可压缩的即时基础，然后我们可以精确地
the signal we have is compressible instant basis and then we can exactly we
instant basis and then we can exactly we construct the originals are underlying
构造原始信号是具有多个
construct the originals are underlying original signal with a number of
original signal with a number of appropriately designed projected
经过适当设计的投影测量，我们可以成为
appropriately designed projected measurement and we can be theta where
measurement and we can be theta where theta is over bed with coefficient and T
θ在床上，系数为T，T为矩阵行，它们是
theta is over bed with coefficient and T is the matrix rows of which are the
is the matrix rows of which are the random with the time projected
与时间投影投影向量随机
random with the time projected projection vector
projection vector so we would like if we assume that this
因此，如果我们假设该V是n维结束的，则以1为基础
so we would like if we assume that this V is n dimensional ended based with one
V is n dimensional ended based with one x and and dimensional n elements and
x和and维n个元素，theta是我们要拥有的n个元素
x and and dimensional n elements and theta is the has n elements we would
theta is the has n elements we would like the number of measurements to be as
比如测量的数量要尽可能少
like the number of measurements to be as low as possible conditions that we have
我们有这些θ系数，我们可以重建我们的图像或信号，
we have these theta coefficients we can reconstruct our image or signal that we
reconstruct our image or signal that we have using an image transport but we
已经使用图像传输，但是我们测量它是一个投影，它是一个
have using an image transport but we measure it is a projection it is a
measure it is a projection it is a projection this problem is undetermined
投影这个问题尚未确定，仍然存在，并且是解决该问题的好方法
projection this problem is undetermined and it still posed and a good way to
and it still posed and a good way to approach this problem is using Bayesian
解决这个问题的方法是使用贝叶斯Setia转换，因此一些结构和
approach this problem is using Bayesian Setia conversion so some structures and
Setia conversion so some structures and we can incorporate this structure of
我们可以结合这个波的这种结构来获得我们的系数
we can incorporate this structure of this wave with to have our coefficients
this wave with to have our coefficients to in order to reduce the number of
为了减少如果我们需要的测量数量
to in order to reduce the number of required measurements that we have if we
required measurements that we have if we want to apply the treatment web
要在信号给晕机上应用治疗网络变换，我们可以
want to apply the treatment web transform on airsick given signal we can
transform on airsick given signal we can define this as deploying the series the
将其定义为部署高通和低通滤波器系列，并且
define this as deploying the series the high-pass and low-pass filters and that
high-pass and low-pass filters and that would result in a quadtree here H stands
将产生四叉树，其中H代表高通，L代表Lopes
would result in a quadtree here H stands for the high-pass and L stands for Lopes
for the high-pass and L stands for Lopes we have a signal with labels will end up
我们有一个带有标签的信号将最终以两种类型的结果开始
we have a signal with labels will end up with two types of results began on each
with two types of results began on each of these we apply these two
在这些中，我们最后使用这两个levan过滤器
of these we apply these two levan filters at the end we end up with
levan filters at the end we end up with three stop bands of death coefficients
如果这是细节中的细节，则三个死亡系数的阻带
three stop bands of death coefficients if this one is the details in the
if this one is the details in the horizontal Direction vertical and
水平方向垂直和对角线区域，这部分是
horizontal Direction vertical and diagonal region and this part is the
diagonal region and this part is the scoring conditions that we have which
给我们评分的条件使我们在宇宙中形成
scoring conditions that we have which gives us the formation in the universe
gives us the formation in the universe space now
现在可以再次构成的空间
space now this can again will be composed again
this can again will be composed again from wavelet coefficients and from
从小波系数到杀死系数，一次又一次
from wavelet coefficients and from killing coefficient and again and again
被称为最后一个是弱音，父母之间的亲子关系
is called the last one is the weak note the parent-child relationship between
the parent-child relationship between the coefficients across each each of
每个系数都有另外四个孩子，直到我们
the coefficients across each each of these have four other children until we
想要使用我们先前在其中合并的结构
would like to use this structure that we have an incorporated in the prior in
have an incorporated in the prior in order to reduce
为了减少测量所需的
order to reduce of measurement that are required for a
of measurement that are required for a basically a good accuracy reconstruction
基本上以前已经对信号进行了良好的精度重建
basically a good accuracy reconstruction of the signal this has been previously
of the signal this has been previously used in other jobs like compressing
用于其他工作，例如压缩电子邮件，压缩数据或纹理
used in other jobs like compressing email compressing data or texture
email compressing data or texture synthesis or image denoising and we
合成或图像去噪，我们想利用此产品
synthesis or image denoising and we would like to take this product exploit
would like to take this product exploit the structure of these wavelet countries
这些小波国家的结构，并在我们的视力倒置中使用它们
the structure of these wavelet countries and use them in our vision inversion one
and use them in our vision inversion one thing about the weblog coefficients is
关于Weblog系数的事情是，Nuke Digital Web Web
thing about the weblog coefficients is that the nuke digital web web
that the nuke digital web web coefficient tend to cluster together and
系数倾向于聚集在一起，并且它们显然可以忽略不计
coefficient tend to cluster together and they apparently a negligible coefficient
they apparently a negligible coefficient it children with high probability would
它的孩子很有可能是0棵树，这意味着父对象是
it children with high probability would be 0 trees it means that the parent is
be 0 trees it means that the parent is doing children is do as 200 so forth and
做孩子大约是200左右
我们可以在多个树中使用隐藏的马尔可夫树进行结构化，我们可以说
be 0 trees it means that the parent is doing children is do as 200 so forth and
we can structure using hidden markov trees in multiple trees we can say that
我们可以在多个树中使用隐藏的马尔可夫树进行结构化，我们可以说
trees in multiple trees we can say that all right
好的，所以我们有两种系数
all right so we have two types of coefficients one
so we have two types of coefficients one unintelligible coefficient you ever try
难以理解的系数，您曾经尝试过可以为我们提供的有效系数
unintelligible coefficient you ever try for the significant coefficients we can
for the significant coefficients we can draw the color negligible coefficient
用低方差从Adelphia绘制颜色可忽略的系数，我们
draw the color negligible coefficient from Adelphia with a low variance and we
from Adelphia with a low variance and we can draw the coefficient significant
可以从高斯中得出系数的显着系数
can draw the coefficient significant coefficients we will from a Gaussian
coefficients we will from a Gaussian with a larger variance and to define
具有更大的方差并定义此父子关系，我们可以
with a larger variance and to define this parent-child relationship we can
this parent-child relationship we can use a markup representation across the
在技​​能上使用标记表示法，因此此标记合适
use a markup representation across the skills so this mark appropriate
skills so this mark appropriate transition can be defined using a two by
可以使用二乘二矩阵P IJ定义跃迁，其中I代表
transition can be defined using a two by two matrix P IJ where I stands for the
two matrix P IJ where I stands for the state of the
接孩子的状态，例如孩子
state of the pick up the child so tij for example kid
pick up the child so tij for example kid Lolo is the probability of child and
Lolo是孩子和父母都处于新状态的概率
Lolo is the probability of child and parents both being in the new state
parents both being in the new state which is a high probability so we show
这是一个很高的概率，所以我们用一个来显示-所有人都是
which is a high probability so we show it with one - extra everyone being a
it with one - extra everyone being a small positive number if parent
如果父系数可忽略，则其子项的正数较小
small positive number if parent coefficients is negligible its children
coefficients is negligible its children would be negligible as well in the tree
在树中我们也可以忽略不计
would be negligible as well in the tree we are assuming that our observations
we are assuming that our observations are our coefficients but in compressive
是我们的系数，但在压缩感测中，我们的测量值是随机的
are our coefficients but in compressive sensing our measurements are the random
sensing our measurements are the random projections of these weather
这些天气系数的投影，我们没有观察到这些
projections of these weather coefficients and we don't observe these
coefficients and we don't observe these coefficients directively directly
假设我们的信号称为X，直接有针对性地确定系数
coefficients directively directly alright assuming our signal is called X
alright assuming our signal is called X we and we have a match basically bevit
我们和我们有一个匹配，基本上是构图，确保它是矩阵Phi
we and we have a match basically bevit the composition make sure it matrix Phi
the composition make sure it matrix Phi we apply this and we get overridden with
我们应用它，我们被系数覆盖，我们的测量结果是
we apply this and we get overridden with coefficients and our measurements are
coefficients and our measurements are random projections of theta M which
θM的随机投影，其中包括有效系数
random projections of theta M which includes the significant coefficients
includes the significant coefficients the negligible ones are set to zero and
可以忽略不计的值设置为零，而另一个为theta e，其中
the negligible ones are set to zero and the other one is theta e where the
the other one is theta e where the natural significant ones are set to zero
自然有效的那些设置为零，而只有可忽略的一个，并且
natural significant ones are set to zero and it only has the negligible one and
and it only has the negligible one and we also assume that we have noise in our
我们还假设我们的测量中有噪声，因此我们可以将其开始
we also assume that we have noise in our measurement so we can start this to our
measurement so we can start this to our and right there at n which is the noise
在n处就是噪声，可以用a表示
and right there at n which is the noise it can be it is represented with a
it can be it is represented with a Gaussian with some precision is the
具有高精确度的高斯是有效的小波系数
Gaussian with some precision is the significant wavelet coefficients first
significant wavelet coefficients first their locations second their values and
他们的位置紧随其后的是价值
[鼓掌]所以这个的后验分布
significant wavelet coefficients first their locations second their values and
[Applause] so the posterior distribution of this
[鼓掌]所以这个的后验分布
so the posterior distribution of this would be inferred using the updated
将使用更新的度量来推断，我们现在这个结构是
would be inferred using the updated measurement we now this structure is a
measurement we now this structure is a structure information that we would like
我们想在我们之前的两个中合并的结构信息
structure information that we would like to incorporate in the prior our two
to incorporate in the prior our two things
亲子关系第二件事
things the parent-child relationship second one
the parent-child relationship second one this person's of the wavelet coefficient
这个人的小波系数可以用这些函数定义
this person's of the wavelet coefficient one can define it using these functions
one can define it using these functions that prior which is a combined
之前的是组合分布和组合
that prior which is a combined distribution and which combined
distribution and which combined attribution which is a built in here is
内置于此的归因是匹配点，并且是高斯
attribution which is a built in here is a match point and and and is a Gaussian
a match point and and and is a Gaussian so we are saying that our rebel
所以我们说我们的反叛系数是从
so we are saying that our rebel coefficients are drawn from there are
coefficients are drawn from there are either zero with probability one minus
要么为零（概率为1减去PI I），要么是从高斯得出的
either zero with probability one minus PI I or they are drawn from a Gaussian
PI I or they are drawn from a Gaussian distribution with some variance with
有概率PI且有一定方差的分布，所以
distribution with some variance with probability PI okay so
probability PI okay so this first part represents the zero
这第一部分代表零系数，而这部分代表
this first part represents the zero coefficient and this part represents the
coefficient and this part represents the significant nonzero coefficient so each
显着的非零系数，所以每个这些都对应一个
significant nonzero coefficient so each of these where are corresponds with one
of these where are corresponds with one of the guardians that really defined we
真正定义我们的监护人是在隐藏的市场中谈论的
of the guardians that really defined we were talking about in the hidden markov
were talking about in the hidden markov tree and here the coefficients in the
树，此处处于低状态的系数设置为零，而不是
tree and here the coefficients in the low state are set to zero as opposed to
low state are set to zero as opposed to hidden markov tree model which is what
隐藏的马尔可夫树模型，每个模型都是从低
hidden markov tree model which is what each was drawn from a Gaussian with low
each was drawn from a Gaussian with low variance now the children will be zero
方差现在，由于对
variance now the children will be zero using some dependences across on the
using some dependences across on the mixing way spike and prior in terms of
混合方式的峰值和先验条件是使用作为元素产品的热水
mixing way spike and prior in terms of using hot water which is element product
using hot water which is element product we have W equals W times W is the
我们有W等于W乘以W是从高斯得出的系数
we have W equals W times W is the coefficient drawn from a Gaussian
coefficient drawn from a Gaussian distribution as Z is a Bernoulli
Z的分布是一个伯努利分布，它是一个或一系列
distribution as Z is a Bernoulli distribution which is the one or series
distribution which is the one or series the one says that
有人说，反叛联盟处于很高的地位
the one says that okay the rebel coalition is in a high
okay the rebel coalition is in a high state and co-state status to low state
状态和共状态从低状态改为设置为零，并且我们的电源
state and co-state status to low state instead set to zero and the power in our
instead set to zero and the power in our model we would like to define this
我们想定义这种混合模型浪费了它们的精度参数
model we would like to define this mixing waste their precision parameter
mixing waste their precision parameter and precision for the noise we can
噪声的精度和精确度，我们可以将模型总结如下：
and precision for the noise we can summarize the model as following we have
summarize the model as following we have our theta it is the product of WS d / w
我们的理论是WS d / w的乘积是来自高斯的有效位置
our theta it is the product of WS d / w is valid position from from a Gaussian
is valid position from from a Gaussian distribution
分布z
distribution z
z is defining whether they are in high or
正在定义它们是处于高位还是低位，这是伯努利分布
is defining whether they are in high or low and it's the Bernoulli distribution
low and it's the Bernoulli distribution and pies are the over basically mixing
馅饼基本上是混合废物，现在我们可以将其划分为
and pies are the over basically mixing mixing waste now we can divide the types
mixing waste now we can divide the types of mixing weights into four categories
混合权重分为四类：一是填充的混合速率
of mixing weights into four categories one is the mixing rate for the filling
one is the mixing rate for the filling coefficient second one is the mixing
系数第二个是他们的真实音符的混合速率，第三个是
coefficient second one is the mixing rate for their real note and third one
rate for their real note and third one is the mixing weight toward the all
是所有其他非零河流条件的混合权重
is the mixing weight toward the all other river conditions that have nonzero
other river conditions that have nonzero basically parents and lastly is the ones
基本上是父母，最后是父母为零的父母，每个父母都是
basically parents and lastly is the ones that have zero parent each of these are
that have zero parent each of these are defined using from hyper trenchers which
定义使用超级挖沟机，通过选择这些超级挖沟机
defined using from hyper trenchers which like to by choosing these hyper
like to by choosing these hyper parameters they would like to say okay
他们想说的参数好吗，我们对缩放有什么想法
parameters they would like to say okay what idea we have about the scaling
what idea we have about the scaling coefficient normally nonzero and we
系数通常为非零，我们希望周围有一些聚类
coefficient normally nonzero and we would like something clustered around
would like something clustered around for the same type of distribution so the
对于相同的分布类型，因此我们希望其父级为零的分布
for the same type of distribution so the ones that have zero parent we would like
ones that have zero parent we would like them to be clustered around 0 and for
它们将聚集在0周围，而其他的非零
them to be clustered around 0 and for the other ones we that have nonzero
the other ones we that have nonzero parents we don't impose any prior
父母，我们不强加任何事先信息，他们可以是这里的任何东西
parents we don't impose any prior information they can be anything here is
information they can be anything here is a graphical representation of the
问题博士的图形表示。模型看到这些是
a graphical representation of the problem dr. model see these are the
problem dr. model see these are the hyper temperatures that we have with
我们使用这个超参数的超温度基本上被使用
hyper temperatures that we have with this hyper parameters are used basically
this hyper parameters are used basically to define the mixing rate and these are
定义混合速率，这些用于定义每个工作站，而V是
to define the mixing rate and these are for defining the per station and V is
for defining the per station and V is our observation here so I describe these
我们在这里的观察，所以我在下面描述这些片段
our observation here so I describe these clips right on
clips right on formulations like all right so the
像这样的公式，所以后验分布参数是
formulations like all right so the posterior distribution parameter here is
posterior distribution parameter here is Theta and this is improv using the
Theta和使用来自海外测量的观察数据即兴
Theta and this is improv using the observed data from overseas measurements
observed data from overseas measurements and we can find the posterior
我们可以使用某种方法找到这个的后验分布
and we can find the posterior distribution for this using some method
distribution for this using some method like a variational Bayesian method
像变分贝叶斯方法马尔可夫链马尔可夫链中的蒙特卡洛
like a variational Bayesian method Markov chain Monte Carlo in a Markov
Markov chain Monte Carlo in a Markov chain Monte Carlo gives a more accurate
链Monte Carlo提供了一个更准确的解决方案，它基本上是
chain Monte Carlo gives a more accurate solution and it is basically
solution and it is basically computationally very expensive on the
另一方面，基于计算的计算非常昂贵
computationally very expensive on the other hand variational based give us a
other hand variational based give us a sum and good approximation to the
求和与解决方案的良好近似值，它快速且具有
sum and good approximation to the solution and it's fast and it has
solution and it's fast and it has convergence criterion and defined which
收敛准则并定义近似真实后验的准则，我们
convergence criterion and defined which approximate the true posterior and we
approximate the true posterior and we have some lower bound f which
有一些下界f，近似于
have some lower bound f which approximates the what the trail of
approximates the what the trail of likelihood and we do iterations until
可能性，然后进行迭代，直到我们几乎不接触DP为止。
likelihood and we do iterations until our little about approaches the DP one
our little about approaches the DP one and the relative reconstruction error is
并使用此方法计算正在计算的相对重建误差
and the relative reconstruction error is calculating is calculated using this
好了，所以这是第一张图片，它是一百28 128张图片和一千张图片
alright so here's the first image it's a hundred 28 128 image and thousand
hundred 28 128 image and thousand measurements have been used we can't
测量已经被使用了，我们基本上不能分解它，然后
measurements have been used we can't basically it's decomposed and then the
basically it's decomposed and then the first coefficient story we constructed
我们构建的第一个系数故事，图像被恢复，这是
first coefficient story we constructed and the image is recovered and this is
and the image is recovered and this is the relative error second image is
相对误差第二个图像通过支持估计值向前倾斜，并且
the relative error second image is tilted forward by support estimate and
tilted forward by support estimate and 2500 measurements have been used for
此测试已使用2500次测量
2500 measurements have been used for this test
this test and the last one is a 32 by 32 image
最后一个是32 x 32的图像，已使用两个图像进行了分解
and the last one is a 32 by 32 image which has been decomposed using two
which has been decomposed using two chocolate reconstructed and then this is
巧克力重建，然后这是错误，我们已经使用了600
chocolate reconstructed and then this is the error and we have used 600
the error and we have used 600 measurements for this all right these
这些的测量这些都是参考，非常感谢
measurements for this all right these are the references and thank you very
are the references and thank you very much any question
很多问题
您好，所有来蒂娜（Tina）的朋友，我正在做我的礼物
are the references and thank you very much any question
hello all visit Tina and I am doing my present
您好，所有来蒂娜（Tina）的朋友，我正在做我的礼物
present on the pairwise chose Michael Chang
在两人选择迈克尔·张（Michael Chang）的情况下，我实际上是通过
on the pairwise chose Michael Chang actually I produced a paper by the
actually I produced a paper by the grooving the Stanford University awarded
在斯坦福大学学习时，获得的奖励比他们向我发布的要多
grooving the Stanford University awarded more than they published it in to me
more than they published it in to me next compliment 2016 which is a you know
下一个恭维2016年这是一个你知道的模型模型离散选择
next compliment 2016 which is a you know the model the model discrete choice
the model the model discrete choice models and there are developing gates
模型，现在加利福尼亚州正在开发盖茨
models and there are developing gates now in California
now in California Caltech used to Berkeley example
加州理工学院曾经以伯克利大学为例，您实际上会看到我
Caltech used to Berkeley example University and you will see actually I
University and you will see actually I want to first of all to I want to bring
首先，我想带来动力，因为模型
want to first of all to I want to bring the motivation about because models
the motivation about because models actually the growing the dataset
实际上，不断增长的数据集包含选择捕获
actually the growing the dataset captaining the choice capturing the
captaining the choice capturing the human children in television especially
电视中的人类儿童，尤其是一些动机和付出的代价
human children in television especially some motivation and some cost for the
some motivation and some cost for the increase meant of the
增加选择模型的含义，以逃避选择
increase meant of the choice model in order to escape from the
choice model in order to escape from the traditional choice period accent for
传统选择时期的口音，例如规律性或随机性
traditional choice period accent for example regularity or stochastic and
example regularity or stochastic and Lucius church action so I want to
卢修斯教会的行动，所以我想讨论介绍的动机
Lucius church action so I want to discuss the motivations for introducing
discuss the motivations for introducing this model prepare watch was Markov
这个模型准备手表是马尔可夫链轻轻地推论它是推论
this model prepare watch was Markov chain is gently model it is inferential
chain is gently model it is inferential interactive graphical model and it does
交互式图形模型，但没有显示我提及公理生产者
interactive graphical model and it does not show me mention axiom producer
not show me mention axiom producer active and insisted upon the foundation
积极并坚持行动提取的基础，因此这种离散
active and insisted upon the foundation of action extraction so this discrete
of action extraction so this discrete choice models destroyed and actually
选择模型被破坏并实际上预测了受害者之间的决定
choice models destroyed and actually predicted the decision between victim
替代方案以及应用程序或消费者购买决策，以及
alternatives and the applications or consumer purchasing decisions and
consumer purchasing decisions and community changes in the mode for
社区改变了向长途运输方式的运输方式
community changes in the mode for transportation to long available options
transportation to long available options so there is a pressing need for
因此迫切需要能够描述
so there is a pressing need for practical model capable of is describing
practical model capable of is describing and predicting the choice behaviour
并预测选择行为
因此，其中一位志愿者实际上可以说是最重要的
practical model capable of is describing and predicting the choice behaviour
so one of the volunteer very actually arguably one of the most important of
因此，其中一位志愿者实际上可以说是最重要的
arguably one of the most important of these excellent to our solutions Church
这些对我们的解决方案非常出色的教会公理，即独立性
these excellent to our solutions Church axiom which is known as the independence
axiom which is known as the independence of irrelevant alternatives
不相关的替代品
因此，举例来说，我们将此公理应用于物质替代品和史密斯
axiom which is known as the independence of irrelevant alternatives
so it's example we applied this axiom on the substance alternatives and Smith
因此，举例来说，我们将此公理应用于物质替代品和史密斯
the substance alternatives and Smith even broader universe you we want to
您想定义一些概率的更广阔的宇宙让pas PD
even broader universe you we want to define some probabilities let pas PD
define some probabilities let pas PD process a chosen from the best beginner
从最佳初学者中选择一个最佳人选，并在基板视图上进行处理；
process a chosen from the best beginner as the best with the substrate view and
as the best with the substrate view and peds the problem chosen a fine chosen
peds问题从这八个事件中选择了一个很好的问题，例如我们
peds the problem chosen a fine chosen from these eight events for example we
from these eight events for example we have two elements there are two
有两个要素每个英语考试都有两个重要的陈述P
have two elements there are two important statement English exam each P
important statement English exam each P AV is equal to zero then pas will be 0
AV等于零，那么对于所有包含和B的进度，pas将为0
AV is equal to zero then pas will be 0 for all contain and B the progress of
for all contain and B the progress of choosing and from you condition on the
选择并根据您的条件选择线上的条件等于3/8，所以另一个
choosing and from you condition on the choice line is equal to 3/8 so another
choice line is equal to 3/8 so another another model easy
另一个模型轻松的布拉德利转宽松模型实际上做了
another model easy Bradley turn loose model actually did
Bradley turn loose model actually did this model I referred it it's got some
我提到的这个模型有一些关于等级封锁的想法
this model I referred it it's got some idea about the rank blocking in detail
idea about the rank blocking in detail comparison so it has been published in
比较，因此它在1956年发布，实际上定义了PAE
comparison so it has been published in 1956 it actually define the PAE
1956 it actually define the PAE and gamma I over gamma a plus gamma
潜在质量参数伦敦之前，伽玛I超过伽玛加伽玛
and gamma I over gamma a plus gamma before latent quality parameters London
before latent quality parameters London gamma I and he resulting
伽玛I和他产生的logit模型员工
gamma I and he resulting logit model employee
logit model employee Visconti parameter gamma i for each i
每个i的Visconti参数gamma i都有您的数目，因此任何模型
Visconti parameter gamma i for each i has the number of you so any model that
has the number of you so any model that satisfied the dilution axiom is a cool
满足稀释公理是一个很酷的不等式
satisfied the dilution axiom is a cool inequities
inequities mmm model so one consequence
mmm模型，所以实际上我在谈论一个结果
mmm model so one consequence actually I am talking about the
actually I am talking about the different models traditional models and
不同的模式，传统的模式和后果，然后我想
different models traditional models and the consequences and then I want to
the consequences and then I want to preach the efficiency and to say that
讲效率，说鸽子做得更好，
preach the efficiency and to say that pigeons is doing a better job and a
pigeons is doing a better job and a great job in comparison to the
与传统的选择模型相比，出色的工作之一是
great job in comparison to the traditional choice model one consequence
traditional choice model one consequence of these lucious action model is a
这些柔和的行为模型之间的随机传递性是
of these lucious action model is a stochastic transitivity between
stochastic transitivity between alternatives chance dignity means for
替代品机会尊严意味着，例如，我们有两个要素，我们有一个
alternatives chance dignity means for example we have two elements we have an
example we have two elements we have an a has a connection with the BBC we can
一个与英国广播公司有联系，我们可以说之间存在音乐关系
a has a connection with the BBC we can say that there is music relation between
say that there is music relation between a and C alternative so it's the
a和C替代，所以PID的概率大于等于
a and C alternative so it's the probability of PID greater than equals
probability of PID greater than equals 1/2 and also the for P then th means
1/2以及P的th均等于或大于营销
1/2 and also the for P then th means equal to or greater than the marketing
equal to or greater than the marketing world ta bian BC a broad important class
世界ta bian BC在贸易展览研究中的重要类别的模型
world ta bian BC a broad important class of models in a study of the trade shows
of models in a study of the trade shows in this ranch house or us or random
在这个牧场房子或我们或随机公用事业模型中，其附属机构每个我
in this ranch house or us or random utility models its affiliates each I at
utility models its affiliates each I at the member of the broader universe you
您和更广泛的宇宙的成员你和一个随机变量I
the member of the broader universe you and a random variable each I and it
and a random variable each I and it defines the probability of our children
定义s的子概率为
defines the probability of our children from s as this expression probability of
from s as this expression probability of X greater than or equal to XJ for any J
对于所有um的任何J，X都大于或等于XJ
X greater than or equal to XJ for any J at all um
at all um don't neither choice as in north the
既不像北方天主教传递性那样选择，所以现在PNC
don't neither choice as in north the Catholic transitivity so now the PNC
Catholic transitivity so now the PNC model it is computationally imple
建模，从概念上讲在计算上是简单的，而复杂的简单
model it is computationally imple conceptually and complicated simple and
conceptually and complicated simple and in fresh a tractable model there are
在新鲜易处理的模型中，有一些参数我们有一些参数
in fresh a tractable model there are some parameters we have some parameters
some parameters we have some parameters in this model the afterburner induced Qi
在此模型中，加力诱发的Qi生成矩阵Q指数值，并且
in this model the afterburner induced Qi generates matrix Q index value and also
generates matrix Q index value and also if this defines the P is the collection
如果这将P定义为替代品的收集概率为
if this defines the P is the collection probability of alternatives as the
probability of alternatives as the probability mass of the genetic eye of
遗传位点的概率质量及其分布
probability mass of the genetic eye of take station and distribution of the
take station and distribution of the continuous time Markov chain the
连续时间马尔可夫链的平稳分布实际上是
continuous time Markov chain the stationary distribution actually the
stationary distribution actually the stationary distribution in the Mark of
平稳分布在变化标记中的概率可以是
stationary distribution in the Mark of change the probability which can be
change the probability which can be shown between Mexico and the in this
显示在墨西哥和这个虚拟的之间，我们有一些问题
shown between Mexico and the in this virtual we have some problems with
virtual we have some problems with distribution coming to one and if if you
分布为一，如果将Phi换位乘以DQ
distribution coming to one and if if you multiply the Phi transpose to DQ between
multiply the Phi transpose to DQ between the rate matrix you get the you get
您获得的费率矩阵就离开了，因此
the rate matrix you get the you get depart so
depart so the station is the reason change to
车站是找到满足固定需求的原因
the station is the reason change to found to satisfy the stationary
found to satisfy the stationary condition of the eminent likelihood
似然函数的条件并建立一个强
condition of the eminent likelihood function and establishing a strong
function and establishing a strong connection between another model and
尽管pcrc模型概括了另一个模型之间的连接
connection between another model and though the pcrc model generalizes
though the pcrc model generalizes disconnection between terminal
终端再营销之间的脱节是Shema所做的
disconnection between terminal remarketing this is the Shema did the
remarketing this is the Shema did the left side is the schematic view of the
左侧是马尔可夫链的四个选择a和b BN c的示意图
left side is the schematic view of the markov chains four choices a and b BN c
markov chains four choices a and b BN c EST those arrows the thickness of those
EST那些箭头的粗细是那些箭头的比率
EST those arrows the thickness of those arrows are the rate the rate of
arrows are the rate the rate of transition the right side is the
过渡的右侧正是这些选择的集合
transition the right side is the assembly of these exactly these choices
assembly of these exactly these choices in the descrition triangle shape Vince
在描述三角形形状的文斯过渡速率中，因此我们定义了一些
in the descrition triangle shape Vince transition rates so we define some
transition rates so we define some actually imposed some constraint here
实际上在这里施加了一些约束，这是他们经历过的一个气
actually imposed some constraint here which is a Qi they've lived through plus
which is a Qi they've lived through plus QJ r is equal to greater than 1 for all
对于所有填充IJ，QJ r均大于1，这是
QJ r is equal to greater than 1 for all fills IJ which is the reducibility in
fills IJ which is the reducibility in short the irreducibility in our model so
简短说明了我们模型的不可约性，因此给定了s并记为
short the irreducibility in our model so given a set s and remember as a
given a set s and remember as a substitute view we want to know we can
我们想知道的替代视图可以通过以下方式控制Cure的构造函数
substitute view we want to know we can control the Cure's constructors by
control the Cure's constructors by restricting you can do that but
限制您可以执行此操作，但要重新训练q 2的行和列
restricting you can do that but retraining the rows and columns of q 2
retraining the rows and columns of q 2 elements instead and set the Q III as
取而代之的是将Q III设置为这样的表达和我们的观点是
elements instead and set the Q III as this expression and peopIe of us is
this expression and peopIe of us is these
这些达到固定分布
these reaching the stationary distribution of
reaching the stationary distribution of people
人们要改变，所以跑步的选择
people to change so the running the choice
to change so the running the choice probability P is which is equal to PI of
P的概率等于I的PI，现在我们要证明
probability P is which is equal to PI of I we now want to show that the piece
I we now want to show that the piece density model is the del define so
密度模型是del定义的，因此我们想证明一个命题
density model is the del define so proposition one we want to show that
proposition one we want to show that these nice choice probabilities are
这些很好的选择概率对于I作为as的成员是明确定义的
these nice choice probabilities are well-defined for the I as a member of as
well-defined for the I as a member of as an all-access as some of you this is
你们当中有些人无所不能，这是某种问题，
an all-access as some of you this is some sort of problem that in order to
some sort of problem that in order to prove it B we need to assume something
证明它B我们需要对我们要证明的目标采取一些假设
prove it B we need to assume something against the target that we want to prove
against the target that we want to prove and continually some contradiction so in
并不断出现一些矛盾，因此为了证明这一点是明确的
and continually some contradiction so in order to prove that this is well-defined
order to prove that this is well-defined I need to show that it there is just
我需要证明，只有一门我们知道的交流课
I need to show that it there is just only one communication class we know
only one communication class we know that s finite so there must be on just
那是有限的，所以这里必须只有一个交流课，所以我知道
that s finite so there must be on just one communication class here so I know
one communication class here so I know that to me more than one through
通过实验课对我来说不止一个，但是我知道
that to me more than one through experimentation class but I know that
experimentation class but I know that face under a disability link constraint
施加残障的残障链接约束下的脸，我知道QIJ
face under a disability link constraint imposing a disability I know that Q I J
imposing a disability I know that Q I J plus 2 J I is greater than or equal to 1
加2 JI大于或等于1，因此这些q IJ中的至少一个或两个
plus 2 J I is greater than or equal to 1 and so at least one of these q IJ or two
and so at least one of these q IJ or two jurors should be strictly positive and
陪审员应该严格肯定，这意味着有一些
jurors should be strictly positive and this implies that there is there is some
this implies that there is there is some screeching distinct communication
努力学习不同的交流课程，等等
screeching distinct communication classes and so
classes and so this is undetermined which would be done
这是不确定的，可以通过变速箱完成
this is undetermined which would be done through the transmission
through the transmission it's tricky positively which is the
肯定是棘手的，这是矛盾的，这里需要注意的是，
it's tricky positively which is the contradictory and some note here is that
contradictory and some note here is that for the irreducibility argument this
对于不可约性参数，此表达式应为正而不是
for the irreducibility argument this expression should be positive not
expression should be positive not necessarily one as I as we brought in
一定是我提出的命题证明中的一个，所以它可以
necessarily one as I as we brought in the proof of our proposition so it could
the proof of our proposition so it could be some constrain like this and for some
像这样的约束，对于某些积极的事物，我们可以乘以
be some constrain like this and for some positive it's belong and we can multiply
positive it's belong and we can multiply by the one origin as a constant and it
一个常数作为常数，它不会影响我们的患者分布
by the one origin as a constant and it does not affect our patient distribution
提议让gamma成为将您孕育的细节的参数
proposition to let gamma be the parameter of the detail mothering you to
parameter of the detail mothering you to chew IJ equal to gamma over gamma plus
咀嚼IJ等于γ超过γ加γJ，请查看进度
chew IJ equal to gamma over gamma plus gamma J please can see progress
gamma J please can see progress experience or consistent because even
经验还是一致的，因为甚至我们的模型，所以我们想证明Pius的
experience or consistent because even our model so we want to show that Pius s
our model so we want to show that Pius s is equal to gamma over the Manhattan
等于伽玛在曼哈顿范数上的伽玛，这是求和
is equal to gamma over the Manhattan norm of the gamma which is the summation
norm of the gamma which is the summation of the gamma a gamma R for I equal to 1
的伽玛R等于I等于1到N，所以我们要表示抱歉
of the gamma a gamma R for I equal to 1 to N so we want to show that sorry we
to N so we want to show that sorry we want to show that that pi is
想要证明pi是...的解释分布
want to show that that pi is interpretation distribution of
interpretation distribution of the chance to change but I will I want
改变的机会，但我要达到的PS传输是平等的
the chance to change but I will I want to reach that PS transmission is equal
to reach that PS transmission is equal to zero so for this expression I have
零，所以对于这个表达式我有一个，所以我们可以拉出这个lambda
to zero so for this expression I have this one so we can pull out this lambda
this one so we can pull out this lambda I and so we know the values of q ji q ji
我所以我们知道q ji q ji的值，所以这里等于零，
I and so we know the values of q ji q ji and here so this is equal to zero that
and here so this is equal to zero that PI RS is always the additional
我现在想将PI RS始终作为链条的附加分销渠道
PI RS is always the additional distribution of the chain now I want to
distribution of the chain now I want to talk about some properties of this piece
谈论这个整体的一些属性，我们想证明
talk about some properties of this piece unity we want to demonstrate that
unity we want to demonstrate that pigeons he exists this structure of the
鸽子，他存在这种第四合同能力的结构，这意味着
pigeons he exists this structure of the fourth contract ability which implies
fourth contract ability which implies uniform expansion so for the universe
均匀扩展，所以对于宇宙的斜线，我们应该谈论两个
uniform expansion so for the universe slash and we should talk about two
slash and we should talk about two definitions first of all first of all it
首先，定义是我的副本的定义
definitions first of all first of all it is the definition of the copies for I
is the definition of the copies for I and J in a structure view we take that
和J在结构视图中，如果
and J in a structure view we take that iron general cookies with each other if
iron general cookies with each other if for all K as the member of s minus I
对于所有K作为s减I减J的成员，我们有以下两个表达式
for all K as the member of s minus I minus J we have these two expressions
minus J we have these two expressions so because there are upper of example
因此，因为有很多例子，KI的记忆选择就没有了
so because there are upper of example choice of memories for K I didn't have
choice of memories for K I didn't have stuff perfectly identified tough stuff
东西完全识别出坚硬的东西，他和K都是相同的牛奶腺
stuff perfectly identified tough stuff he and K identical glands of milk so
he and K identical glands of milk so they say it's her niche content that the
他们说读者使用某种类型的概率是她的利基内容
they say it's her niche content that the probability that the reader uses a type
probability that the reader uses a type of beverage in this scenario it is the
在这种情况下的饮料数量与仅显示一个饮料的情况相同
of beverage in this scenario it is the same as if they was shown just only one
same as if they was shown just only one cup of some sort of the beverage and
一杯某种饮料，并且无论k的值等于
cup of some sort of the beverage and regardless of the the values of k equal
regardless of the the values of k equal to or greater than one definition to is
等于或大于一个定义为是均匀展开，因为
to or greater than one definition to is the uniform expansion because there a
the uniform expansion because there a choice between an element in a set as
从爱荷华州一个元素中选择一个元素，然后熨烫一个元素，然后
choice between an element in a set as one from Iowa one to iron one and
one from Iowa one to iron one and another choice promise that okay
另一个选择承诺，包含K cookie的好东西会爱上每个
another choice promise that okay containing K cookie love each of those
containing K cookie love each of those and n elements the axiom of uniform
和n个元素分别表示M和所有K的均匀扩张状态的公理
and n elements the axiom of uniform expansion States as put each M and all K
expansion States as put each M and all K greater than or equal to 1 we have this
大于或等于1我们有这个表达式
greater than or equal to 1 we have this expression
因此我们得出结论，PTSD模型仅表现出更一般的特性
so we conclude that PTSD model only exhibiting more general property of
exhibiting more general property of contract ability which it's always
收缩能力，总是表现出均匀的膨胀，所以我想要
contract ability which it's always exhibit uniform expansion so me I want
exhibit uniform expansion so me I want to hear bring the preposition tree for
聆听给定伽玛的介词树，这就是lambda IJ让
to hear bring the preposition tree for given gamma which is the lambda IJ let
given gamma which is the lambda IJ let a1 to a2 be a contractible partition for
a1到a2是PT的可收缩分区，与您所代表的分区相似
a1 to a2 be a contractible partition for to PT and similar than you represented
to PT and similar than you represented by Q and Q Prime with the station
由Q和Q Prime使用工作站分布Python，然后针对任何AI
by Q and Q Prime with the station distribution Python then for any AI we
distribution Python then for any AI we have this expression or equivalently we
有这个表达式或等效地，我们说PI AI等于-嘿Ari所以
have this expression or equivalently we say that PI AI is equal to - hey Ari so
say that PI AI is equal to - hey Ari so for the proof these patrols that Q has
为了证明这些巡逻，Q相对于
for the proof these patrols that Q has partition a 1 to a K with respect to
partition a 1 to a K with respect to gamma if it be composed the balanced
伽马如果由平衡方程组成未来美德的各定律
gamma if it be composed the balanced equation each law of the future virtue
equation each law of the future virtue which is equal to 0 for each member of a
对于1的每个成员等于0而又不失一般性
which is equal to 0 for each member of a 1 without loss of generality we can
1 without loss of generality we can obtain these expression so
获得这些表达式，这样
这里要注意的是，对于印度的一小片地区，首都地区的成员和同性恋者
1 without loss of generality we can obtain these expression so
here noting that for the a small area in India the member of Capital Area and gay
这里要注意的是，对于印度的一小片地区，首都地区的成员和同性恋者
India the member of Capital Area and gay and AJ is equal to lambda IJ here we can
并且AJ等于lambda IJ在这里我们可以实际分解它
and AJ is equal to lambda IJ here we can we can actually decompose it
we can actually decompose it multivariate each coil 60 each of these
在这个表达式中将每个线圈60多变量这些项中的每一项，然后得出
multivariate each coil 60 each of these terms in this expression and then coming
terms in this expression and then coming over act as a member of a one we we will
作为一个成员的行为，我们将达到这个长表达
over act as a member of a one we we will reach this this long expression the
reach this this long expression the leftmost Titanic II studies equal so
最左边的泰坦尼克号II研究相等，所以这一项和这一项，我们可以
leftmost Titanic II studies equal so this one and this one so we have we can
this one and this one so we have we can get the PA one which which makes the pay
得到一个PA，它使一个人的工资作为解决方案
get the PA one which which makes the pay feed upon a one as the solution to
平衡方程以上命题与协调契约的能力。
balanced equation the above proposition and the concert the contract the ability
and the concert the contract the ability of efficiency model so it implies that
模型的效率，因此它暗示PDMP模型表现出统一的
of efficiency model so it implies that the PDMP model exhibits uniform
the PDMP model exhibits uniform expansion
扩张
印度人的推理和预测部分是我们的最终目标是通过谴责它
the PDMP model exhibits uniform expansion
Indians inference and prediction part our ultimate goal is through berating it
印度人的推理和预测部分是我们的最终目标是通过谴责它
our ultimate goal is through berating it model to make predictions using past
建模以使用过去从不同子集中的选择进行预测
model to make predictions using past choices from different subsets to
choices from different subsets to predict future choices there are three
预测未来的选择，其中三分之三接受印度
predict future choices there are three part three accept India in the
part three accept India in the prediction part leaving the no blank
预测部分，留下无空白函数，即速率矩阵Q
prediction part leaving the no blank function which is the rate matrix Q
function which is the rate matrix Q given a choice data collection of the
给定形式T的选择数据集合，其中IK是SK的成员
given a choice data collection of the form T where the I K is the member of SK
form T where the I K is the member of SK was the eyes and chosen from escaped
是眼睛，是从逃脱的调查中选择的，了解每个人的能力
was the eyes and chosen from escaped investigating the ability of learnt each
investigating the ability of learnt each day and tomorrow to make choice
每天和明天根据经验数据基准进行选择预测
day and tomorrow to make choice prediction on empirical data benchmark
prediction on empirical data benchmark against learn ml and then interpreting
反对学习毫升，然后解释内容丰富的诺言
against learn ml and then interpreting the informative promises to have for the
the informative promises to have for the muscular fluids
让我们将T定义为项目的数量
muscular fluids let's define T is as the number of items
let's define T is as the number of items number of times in the data that I was
从成功中选择我的数据的次数，我也将其视为
number of times in the data that I was chosen from the success I also see it as
chosen from the success I also see it as the number of times that X was chosen
如上所讨论，为每个X选择X的次数，因此
the number of times that X was chosen for each as discussed above you so there
for each as discussed above you so there are two recordings here for each as if P
这里有两个录音，就好像P是Q是
are two recordings here for each as if P is a Q is the probability for the
is a Q is the probability for the selection of s as a function of the rate
随利率市场q的变化而选择s，然后将所有
selection of s as a function of the rate market q and after dropping all the
market q and after dropping all the constants the loaf likely would have Q
给定数据T时，面包可能具有Q的常数
constants the loaf likely would have Q given the data T which have been here
given the data T which have been here derived from the probability
从多项式分布的概率函数得出
derived from the probability function of the multinomial distribution
function of the multinomial distribution which is and we get this expression and
就是这个，我们得到这个表达式并记录到第45个条目中
which is and we get this expression and for the recording to the 45th entry
for the recording to the 45th entry model we have we want to be we have D
模型，我们要成为我们，我们要拥有D净化器是我们的关注点
model we have we want to be we have D the purifier is the attention
the purifier is the attention distribution for the continuous time
连续时间马尔可夫链的分布，实际上他们有它们
distribution for the continuous time Markov chain and actually they have they
Markov chain and actually they have they have used the non taped problem
已经使用了非录音问题的优化问题，如果有人
have used the non taped problem optimization problem and if anyone is
optimization problem and if anyone is interested just for the informational
只是对他们使用SLS Q感兴趣的信息感兴趣
interested just for the informational thing that they have used the SLS Q
thing that they have used the SLS Q programming the credential it is for
对凭证进行编程，以便对它们进行优化
programming the credential it is for programming in order to optimize them
programming in order to optimize them they use the type file that minimize a
他们使用类型文件来最小化Python中的函数，或者您可以使用
they use the type file that minimize a function in the Python or you can use
function in the Python or you can use the minimize the method the security
最小化方法的安全性
那里有经验数据结果，他们评估了程序，还有三个
function in the Python or you can use the minimize the method the security
there the empirical data results they evaluate the procedure and three
那里有经验数据结果，他们评估了程序，还有三个
evaluate the procedure and three empirical data sets from surveillance
来自San周围交通运输监督调查的经验数据集
empirical data sets from surveillance survey of Transportation around the San
survey of Transportation around the San Francisco Bay Area
旧金山湾地区旧金山战争受到遏制
Francisco Bay Area the San Francisco war is contained
the San Francisco war is contained twelve thousand twenty nine of the
该关系的一万二千二百九十九个由社区选择组成
twelve thousand twenty nine of the relation consists of community options
relation consists of community options and the choice mode on a given community
以及给定社区的选择模式，因为我们将包含3157
and the choice mode on a given community and as we shall contain 3157
and as we shall contain 3157 observations each consistent choice set
观察每个可供选择的运输备选方案的一致选择
observations each consistent choice set of transportation alternatives available
of transportation alternatives available to individuals traveling and returning
给从购物中心旅行和返回的个人
to individuals traveling and returning from a shopping center
为了使我们的现代观察成为可能，她进行了培训和评估
for the training for turning our modern observation she trained and evaluate
observation she trained and evaluate unattested
未经认证的老师，这是
unattested teachers this is be the bearer of
teachers this is be the bearer of teacher and teachers that we want to
老师和我们要评估的老师实际上是比较厨房
teacher and teachers that we want to evaluate actually comparative kitchens
evaluate actually comparative kitchens amount of a conditional be others model
在此表达式中，有条件的其他人的数量为Q
amount of a conditional be others model beach in in this expression the Q
beach in in this expression the Q hottest teacher an estimate for view
最热的老师从对厨房和厨房的观察中获得的视野估计值
hottest teacher an estimate for view obtained from observation of kitchen and
obtained from observation of kitchen and P tilde is theta is equal to cos
P tilde是theta等于截至今天为止熟练的cos老师
P tilde is theta is equal to cos teachers who were skilled as of today
teachers who were skilled as of today which is the empirical probability of I
从比例中选择I的经验概率
which is the empirical probability of I was selected from as among of the ratio
was selected from as among of the ratio cheetahs this is actually I have done it
猎豹，这实际上是我首先为一些弗朗西斯做的
cheetahs this is actually I have done it for first of all for some Frances to
for first of all for some Frances to work data and first the number of
工作数据，首先是错误的模拟数量，这是十，这是
work data and first the number of simulations wrong it's ten this is the
simulations wrong it's ten this is the comparison between the error versus the
误差与用于训练的数据百分比之间的比较
comparison between the error versus the percentage of data used for training
percentage of data used for training from five to seventy five percent
从百分之五到百分之七十五的百分之十九
from five to seventy five percent nineteen seventy five percent of the
nineteen seventy five percent of the data for training and 25 for the test
训练数据，25个测试数据和15个模型都做得很好
data for training and 25 for the test and fifteen see model is doing great job
and fifteen see model is doing great job hearing in comparison to mmm a nano
相较于mmm，您会听到纳米混合器的声音，他的热量是
hearing in comparison to mmm a nano mixer manner and his are they the heat
mixer manner and his are they the heat match for the forty probability for each
匹配每一侧实际水平和垂直的四十概率
match for the forty probability for each side actually horizontal and vertical we
side actually horizontal and vertical we have dick
鸡巴，我们选择了苍白的选择
have dick we have picked pale of the options which
we have picked pale of the options which are driving alone and sharing around
独自开车，彼此共享，先在公共场所工作
are driving alone and sharing around with one another first to work in public
with one another first to work in public transit biking and carpooling with at
与至少两个其他人一起骑行和拼车的过境活动，我们正在展示
transit biking and carpooling with at least two others and we are showing the
least two others and we are showing the probability of need relative risk rate
成对项目之间的相对风险率的需求概率以及如何
probability of need relative risk rate between pairs of items as well as how
between pairs of items as well as how the total rates between first and
在这里编辑其他页面的第一位和个人导师之间的总费用I
the total rates between first and personal tutor editing other page here I
personal tutor editing other page here I did the simulation for number of equal
进行了等于50的模拟，所以当我们激活时
did the simulation for number of equal to 50 so when we activate when we
to 50 so when we activate when we increase the number of stimulation it
增加刺激的数量将与上一个刺激相同
increase the number of stimulation it will be so in the previous one with the
will be so in the previous one with the tenth simulation we see here that first
第十次仿真，我们在这里看到，我们的TNT模型的第一个开始更多
tenth simulation we see here that first of our TNT model starts with little more
of our TNT model starts with little more but then we increase the increase the
但是随后我们增加了开始模拟的次数
but then we increase the increase the number of simulations they start on
number of simulations they start on something the same but after that
相同的东西，但是相比其他效率模型
something the same but after that efficiency model in comparison to other
efficiency model in comparison to other mothers during the great job so even in
母亲们在出色的工作中，即使在违反IIA的数据中，
mothers during the great job so even in data with violations of iia that was the
data with violations of iia that was the that was known for the lucia first axiom
以最近我谈论的露西亚第一公理而闻名，这是
that was known for the lucia first axiom that i talked about lately which is the
that i talked about lately which is the independence relevant of alternatives
与替代品相关的独立性PMT的性能提高20％到30％
independence relevant of alternatives PMT does 20 to 30 percent better at
PMT does 20 to 30 percent better at prediction out-of-sample without
预测超出样本，且不违反PT，然后返回到
prediction out-of-sample without violations PT and is followed back to a
violations PT and is followed back to a manner and is it for san francisco shock
方式，是否用于旧金山冲击数据，并再次访问八分之八？
manner and is it for san francisco shock data and again visit for eight of eight
data and again visit for eight of eight actually ordered options and previous
实际订购的选件和之前的将近60件，因此这里再次为15 T型号
actually ordered options and previous almost 60 so here again the 15 T model
almost 60 so here again the 15 T model is doing better than two other models
比其他两个模型做得更好
所以我们可以说，随着学习程序的应用，数据上的错误
almost 60 so here again the 15 T model is doing better than two other models
so which we can say that error on the data as the learning procedures applied
所以我们可以说，随着学习程序的应用，数据上的错误
data as the learning procedures applied to increase the amount of data the
增加数据量，结果平均超过1,000
to increase the amount of data the results are averaged over 1,000
results are averaged over 1,000 different permutations of the data to be
应变和文本数据在7520中数据的不同排列
different permutations of the data to be in the 7520 upon strain and text data
in the 7520 upon strain and text data prediction error on a 25 percent hold of
PNC M＆L和mmm混合数据保留25％的预测误差
prediction error on a 25 percent hold of the data for the PNC M&amp;L and mmm mix
the data for the PNC M&amp;L and mmm mix terminal models have been shown and 50
终端模型已经显示出来，而50毫克母亲的这些改善了30
terminal models have been shown and 50 mg mother's these improvement of thirty
mg mother's these improvement of thirty five point nine percent and twenty four
五分百分之九的百分之二十四点百分之五的预测误差
five point nine percent and twenty four point five percent in prediction error
point five percent in prediction error over M&amp;L and mix terminal respectively
在M＆L和混合终端上训练时，分别训练百分之七十五
over M&amp;L and mix terminal respectively when training on seven five percent as a
when training on seven five percent as a danger for this summary we introduced a
危险的是，我们介绍了一个非常明智的选择马尔可夫链模型，并且
danger for this summary we introduced a very wise choice Markov chain models and
very wise choice Markov chain models and the speed choice which define selection
根据断言定义选择属性的速度选择
the speed choice which define selection properties according to the assertion
properties according to the assertion distribution of a continuous time Markov
连续时间的分布马尔可夫链的灵活性
distribution of a continuous time Markov chains the flexibility for which the
chains the flexibility for which the flexibility we demonstrate that tthe
灵活性，我们证明该模型展现出理想的结构是
flexibility we demonstrate that tthe model exhibits desirable structure was
model exhibits desirable structure was preceding the uniform expansion property
之前仅在M＆L模型中发现的均匀膨胀特性之前
preceding the uniform expansion property previously found only in the M&amp;L model
previously found only in the M&amp;L model and elimination by aspects model the
和消除方面建模工作状态，厨房
and elimination by aspects model the working on states that the kitchen
working on states that the kitchen remodel exhibits concern
改型表现出关注的可建设性，这意味着统一
remodel exhibits concern constructability which implies uniform
constructability which implies uniform expansion we have to show that the
扩展，我们必须证明鸽子的报价数量
expansion we have to show that the pigeons amount of offers
pigeons amount of offers thenceforward inference through Emily
然后通过艾米丽（Emily）进行推论，这将学习代理模型
thenceforward inference through Emily and that will learn the agency model
and that will learn the agency model predicts
预测会改善她的选择
predicts improve her choice it will be
improve her choice it will be significantly higher utility the respect
与其他两种型号相比，实用性高得多
significantly higher utility the respect to two other models
to two other models for the future because this is a very
对于未来，因为这是样本组的一个非常新颖的想法，
for the future because this is a very novel idea by the sample group the
novel idea by the sample group the possibility and tractability of the PCs
PC的可能性和易处理性该模型开放了许多计算
possibility and tractability of the PCs the model opens up many computing
the model opens up many computing research directions the efficiency of
研究方向TMC模型的效率建议探索其他
research directions the efficiency of the TMC model suggests exploring other
the TMC model suggests exploring other effective parameterization for q the
q的有效参数化速率矩阵，包括展开L
effective parameterization for q the rate matrix including developing L
rate matrix including developing L special methods which excludability
排他性的特殊方法有两个开放式计算
special methods which excludability there are two open computational
there are two open computational questions such as extremely large lining
诸如极大衬里的大型Luud最大化之类的问题
questions such as extremely large lining the large Luud maximization using
the large Luud maximization using gradients of the implicit function
隐式函数定义的渐变，这些是参考
gradients of the implicit function definitions and these are the references
definitions and these are the references for for this room thank you
对于这个房间谢谢
[掌声]
definitions and these are the references for for this room thank you
[Applause]